[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "What was going on there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Well, she's a wonderful woman who I've gotten to know over the years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Which was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "It was a very interesting evening.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Is that something you would ever consider?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "I don't see that happening from either of our standpoints actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "RB", "CC", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "What do you make of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Well, I was a little surprised by that debate, because, all of a sudden, he comes out of nowhere and starts going crazy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "I mean, would you 100 percent recognize yourself in a similar image?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "Well, I'd know if somebody had a picture of me, you know, in that position and wearing those clothes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "What did you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Well, I was very surprised.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "What's your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Well, I don't know him at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "If he emerges, Donald, final, if he emerges as the Republican choice, as their nominee, would that make you more or less tempted to run as an independent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Well, I'd have to see how he emerges.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "What is it about this story that has gripped America, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Well, Piers, that's an excellent question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "I mean, given all your experience with these kinds of things, Nancy, do you think there's much doubt that she was responsible for the death of her daughter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Well, in my mind, based on the evidence that I have heard, and I've still got to hear the rest.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nancy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Casey"]}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Does it have any credibility when you do that kind of thing in a courtroom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "Well, look, I think they could have made a credible defense argument here and that argument would have been that this was an accident, that the child drowned or the child hurt herself, or something happened where it was an accident, and that Casey then sort of lost it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "What do you think the next step's going to be in this case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Well, you know, Piers, every day, the defense astounds me by what they do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Dan, let me ask you, finally -- just running out of time here -- Dan, if you were prosecuting this, based on everything you've seen and heard so far, would you be feeling pretty optimistic of a conviction now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", ":", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", "RB", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", ",", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Whether you're Arnold Schwarzenegger, whether you're the guy from IMF, obviously, more serious, whether you're Anthony Weiner -- when you go through something so public and humiliating in so many ways, what's the best way to dust yourself down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Well, tell the truth.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IMF"], "PERSON": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger", "Anthony Weiner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "What kind of job is Barack Obama doing as president of your country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Well, I love it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin", "Donald Trump", "Jerry Springer"]}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "What kind of people are we to say that's not a good thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Well, we're going to come back after break and discuss one of those people, Sarah Palin and Donald Trump and a few other of the leading political lights, and get the Jerry Springer verdict.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "What would you make of President Trump as an option for America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Well, I like the man.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Vietnam"]}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "You worked with him on Miss Universe, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "Yes, the year we did it in Vietnam.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Miss Universe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Why don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "One, I don't agree with his views.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "America needs some bravado, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Well, it is so momentary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "What do you make of her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "She connects.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "What do you think of those two candidates?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Here's the thing: a candidate is never as popular as he is or she is the moment before they announce.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Pawlenty"]}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Where would your money be on a Republican candidate right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "I'd say right now it would be either Pawlenty or Romney.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "So technically you can't be president, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "Right, not because I was born in the subway, but because I was born in England.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Where did you get these?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "I watched a very moving interview you did in Britain actually about the whole situation with your family and the Holocaust and the number of relatives that you lost to that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "``", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 586, "question": "And where did I get that hair?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "Let me ask you a tricky question, because I've known you a long time and we're good friends and we worked together on \"America's Got Talent.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "Am I right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "What did you mean by that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Well, partly tongue in cheek.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "Why do you keep doing it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "I told you, one, I enjoy it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110601pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "Snobbery?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]